Guide to the Internation Brotherhood of Teamsters Graphic Communications Conference records, 1902-2006 IBT0006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Public Information Department - William Moody Research files, 1902-2006; Series 1; 29.25 Linear Feet
  - Senators (Elections), 1973-1976; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Seniority - Labor Conference, 1975; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Service Employees International Union - re. 16th am., 1976; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Sex Discrimination, 1980; Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Shanker, Al - Teachers syndical movement, 1973-1975; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - SHAPE - Safety and Health Awareness Announcement Program for Employees and Employers, 1978,1980,1982; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Siderography - Merger, 1971; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Sir Speedy Center, 1984; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Situs Picketing Bill, 1975; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Slides/GAIU, Undated; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Sluce, Victor, 1985; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Smith - Edwards - Dunlap Operating Services Information Department, 1975; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Social Credit and Government Canada, 1984; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Social Democrats, USA, 1975,1980; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Social Security/Medicare, 1968-1971,1981; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Solidarity Forever, Undated; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Somalia (Apri - Rustin Article), 1981; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Southern state Conference, 1976,1985; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Editors Visit, 1986; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Sparta Local 785S, 1983,1985; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Springfield Graphic Ohio, 1972,1973; Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Staff Union, 1985; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Standard Studios Photgraphers, 1965-1983; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Standing Committee of Trade Union in the Graphic Industry - Bulletin, 1982; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - State Paper Tax, 1983; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - State, county, and minucipal Employees, PM fed of AESME, 1975-1986; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Steelworkers United, 1973-1987; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Stereotypers' and Electrotypers' Union of North America, 1966-1972; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Stereotypers and Electrotypers International Union - ISEU Journal, 1970-1971; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Stone, Donald, 1961-1974; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Streeter, Daniel, 1965-1978; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Strikes - General, 1967-1978,1985; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Strikes - IAM (airline strike), 1966; Series 1 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Strikes - kingsport Press, 1966,1974; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Strikes - Wilkes-Barne Newspaper Strike, 1978-1984; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - St. Joseph 529, 1981,1982; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - St. Louis Locals 505 252, 1966-1967,1982,1986; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - St. Paul Local 29C, 1984; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Subscription - complimentary, 1967-1987; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Subscription - mailing list, 1966-1985; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Supplemental Retirement and Disabilty Fund, 1964-1983; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan (Canada), 1977,1981; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Syracuse Local 284m, 1983,1985; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Sylvis, William H, 1969; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Tacoma Local 49N, 1984; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Taft-Hartley Act, 1947,1972; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Taxes, 1969-1973; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Taylor Law, New York State, 1968; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters, International Brotherhood of, 1967-1987; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Technological Div. Comm ALA, LPIU, 1962-1968; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Technological Development Ed Comm. GAIU, 1973; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Television: Corporate America's Game, ND (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - The American Federationist, 1972-1974 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - The Butcher Workman, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - The Economy in Contrast: Nixon-Ford Years vs. Kennedy-Johnson Years, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - The Carter Welfare Plan: A Critical Analysis, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - The Graphic Arts International Union: The Sign of the Times in Printing, ND (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - "This is Our Union" Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - 3M Correspondence, 1967,1969,1972,1974; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - 3M General, 1963,1964,1966,1967,1968; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - three M - 3M, 1972-1974; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - To Clear the Record AFL-CIO Executive Council Report on the Disaffiliation of the UAW, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Torrence, Bill, 1983 October 18; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Toronto Locals 18C,12L,28L,211,580M, 1980-1986; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Trade Bill (Burke/Hartke), 1973; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Trademark (GAIU), 1973; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Trade Union Advertising Inc., 1971-1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Trade Union Education Committee, 1984; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Training Directors, 1971; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Tri Cities Local 382, 1982,1983; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Trustees (Special Joint Trust Institute), 1972-1974; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Typographical Union (ITU), 1965-1980; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Typesetters, 1961-1980; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - UAW Solidarity, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - UFCW Constitution and Merger Agreement, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - UFCW Leadership Update Special Report, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Union Busting, 1976-1980; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Union Busting, 1979-1981; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Union Busting, 1978-1980,1985; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Union Industries Show, 1967-1973; Series 1 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Union Industries Show, 1967-1978; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Union Label - General, 1965-1977; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Union Label - General, 1965-1977; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Union Labor Life Insurence (JLLICO) - General, 1967-1988; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Union Labor Life Insurence (JLLICO) - Annual Reports, 1966-1984; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Union Labor Life Insurence (JLLICO) - Bulletin, 1970-1980; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Union Printmakers, 1977,1979; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - United Nations - UN We Believe, 1974-1975; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - United Nations Assosiation - Econ Policy Council, 1978; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - United Transportation Union, 1969,1973,1986; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - United Transportation Worker Union Merger Pack, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - United Way, 1979,1982; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Universal Product Code, 1976; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Vangarden, Walter P., 1984; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Vermont Labor History Society, 1986 June; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Vietnam War, 1966-1970; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Volz, edward J, 1964-1968; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Wage Guidelines, 1966; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Wallace, George - Memo From COPE, 1968,1975; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Wallace, Jack H., 1972; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Warmke, Norman C., 1978; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Washington DC Local 42B - EEOC suit, 1980-1981; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Washington DC Local 285 - News Letters, 1982-1985; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Washington Post Pressmen's Strike, 1976; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Watergate: Labor Press, Meet The Press, 1974; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Watergate - Article from The Nation, The new Republic and US News + World Report, 1974; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Watson, Merris, 1966; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Web Offset Technology, 1964; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Western Publishing - Trademark Infringment Letter, 1967,1974; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - westvaco and West Virginia Pulp and Paper Co., 1966,1972-1976; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - What's Libel? A Guide for Local Union Editors, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - Wickersham, L.M., 1962-1984; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Wide World Photos, 1965-1986; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Wilson, Russel S., 1972; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Winpisinger, Willian W - SANE Peace Award Speech, 1979; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Wirtz, Willard W., 1968; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Working Women - General, 1972-1982; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Women in Book Binding - Project For Equal Progression, 1975-1976; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Women In Book Binding - Project For Equal Programming, 1975-1976; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Women's Auxilary, 1964-1974; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Women's International Auxilary - News 'n Views, 1965-1967; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Wood, Saundra, 1978,1981; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Work Week - Shorter, 1971-1972; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Work Week - Shorter, 1961,1977,1979; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Zack, Al, 1975,1978; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Pressmens's Local 22, Denver, 1938-1964; Series 2
  This series contains agreements between Pressmen's Local 22 and various printing companies in the Denver, Colorado, area.
  This series is arranged by individual agreement and identified by the year the agreement was signed.
  Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor; Labor unions
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1938; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1942; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1940; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1946; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1941; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1940; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1941; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1945; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1938; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1942; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1939; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1940; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1938; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1938; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1951; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1938; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1939; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1939; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1950; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1950; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1947; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1946; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1946; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1946; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1946; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1942; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1947; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1946; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1946; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1948; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1946; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1947; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1948; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1964; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1948; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1941-1948; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1945; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1948; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1951; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 41)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1947; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 42)
  - Graphic Communications Conference Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, 1953; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 43)
- Graphic Communicator Magazine, 1983-1998; Series 3
  This series coontains issues of The Graphic Communicator, the monthly journal of the Graphic Communications International Union which merged with the IBT, Volumes 1-16.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 1, 1983 (Box 61, Item 1)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 2, 1984 (Box 61, Item 2)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 3, 1985 (Box 61, Item 3)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 4, 1986 (Box 62, Item 1)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 5, 1987 (Box 62, Item 2)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 6, 1988 (Box 62, Item 3)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 7, 1989 (Box 63, Item 1)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 8, 1990 (Box 63, Item 2)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 9, 1991 (Box 63, Item 3)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 10, 1992 (Box 63, Item 4)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 11, 1993 (Box 63, Item 5)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 12, 1994 (Box 64, Item 1)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 13, 1995 (Box 64, Item 2)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 14, 1996 (Box 64, Item 3)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 15, 1997 (Box 64, Item 4)
  - Graphic Communicator Magazine Volume 16, 1998 (Box 64, Item 5)
- Miscellaneous Files, 1965-2011; Series 4
  This series is arranged by subject.
  This series contains miscellaneous materials pertaining to the Graphic Communications Conference of Teamsters.
  - GCC / IBT Constitution and Laws, 2011; IBT0006 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - GCC / IBT Proceedings of the Second Convention, 2011; IBT0006 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - GCC / IBT Logo Magnet, Undated; IBT0006 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - GCIU Proceedings of the Founding Convention, 1984; IBT0006 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Graphic Communicator Newspaper, 2005-2014; IBT0006 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - ITU Review Newspaper, 1984; IBT0006 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Keep America Working, Buy American Products Sticker, Buy Union Card, IBT 0006 Series 4 (Flat box 67, Folder 3)
  - LPIU First Convention Media Kit, 1965; IBT0006 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Solidarity with Solidarnosc Sticker, IBT 0006 Series 4 (Flat box 67, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Badge's and Pins, IBT 0006 Series 4 (Flat box 67, Folder 1)
  - Teamster Stickers: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Trainmen (Flat box 67, Folder 4)
  - Graphic Communication Conference [Info-Sheet], Undated; Series 4 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 1)